<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <!-- changelog for the release branch -->
  <string name="changelog_release" translatable="false"><Data><![CDATA[<div>
<h1>2021.04.11-RC (Beta):</h1>

<h3>
We had to do extensive changes to the way c:geo gets access to your file system (e.g. for storing data, reading offline maps) to be prepared for requirements on new Android versions.
After upgrading to this c:geo version a wizard will guide you through the needed changes. Please follow these steps carefully!
<br>
Refer to <a href="https://faq.cgeo.org/#SAF">this FAQ entry</a> for more information.
</h3>

<h4>Map:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Change: Merged \"show direction\" and \"Routing mode\" settings (map quick settings popup)</li>
<li>New: Added OpenAndroMaps to map downloader (for offline map files and map themes). Alternatively you can also use the \"Install others\" links on openandromaps.org website</li>
<li>New: Added Freizeitkarte to map downloader (for offline map files and map themes)</li>
<li>New: Multi-threaded rendering for OpenStreetMap maps (optional)</li>
<li>New: Support for zipped theme files - you do not have to unzip map theme files any longer, just put the zip file into your theme folder</li>
<li>Fix: Respect \"show circles\" setting when switching from OSM map to Google map</li>
<li>Fix: Reset circle color in OSM maps on color change in settings</li>
</ul>

<h4>Cache details:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Change: Renamed menu entries to distinguish between "remove cache(s) from this list" and "delete cache(s) from device", depending on currently selected list - no change in behavior</li>
<li>Change: Scale offline log images on upload only</li>
<li>New: Swipe down to refresh cache details and trackable list</li>
<li>New: Long-click on waypoint coordinates to copy them to clipboard</li>
<li>New: On navigate-drive show final with different coordinates as separate target</li>
<li>New: Include traditional chinese translation</li>
</ul>

<h4>Other:</h4>
<ul>
<li>New: Set user-defined coords for waypoints on GPX import even when original waypoint has no coords</li>
<li>New: Add support for cache attributes in locus connector</li>
<li>New: Export and import UDC with empty coordinates</li>
<li>New: Add toggle to pocket query list on mainscreen to display all/downloadable pocket queries only</li>
<li>Fix: Minor bug fixes for the numbers template, when used by the Twitter plug-in</li>
<li>Fix: Adapt to website change for \"spotted by\" trackables</li>
<li>Fix: Show actual cache marker in OSM map multi-marker popup</li>
<li>Fix: Prevent adding duplicate images when using Google Photos</li>
<li>Fix: Remove \"Cancel\" from list selection to make the other items fit in one row</li>
<li>Fix: Opening GPX files from some mail clients did not offer c:geo as target app</li>
</ul>

</ul>

</div>]]></Data>
</string>
</resources>
