<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <!-- changelog for the master branch -->
  <string name="changelog_master" translatable="false"><Data><![CDATA[<div>
<h1>Nightly build:</h1>

<h4>Android 11 notice:</h4>
Android 11 enforces a new way for storing data, which c:geo does not support yet. For the time being c:geo is using a legacy method to access data on the storage system (e.g. offline maps, imports/exports of GPX, backups, field notes) which seems to work well with Android 11. In parallel we are continuously working to implement the changes enforced by Google for the storage access in future c:geo versions. If you notice any issues on your Android 11 device, please kindly let us know on our support channels.

<h4>Map:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Change: Old mapsforge map has been disabled and will be removed in future releases.</li>
<li>Change: Moved \"Combined (Offline)\" map entry to top of offline maps</li>
<li>Change: Removed restrictions on initial zoom level</li>
<li>Fix: Missing information (eg.: hint) for stored caches when in live map mode</li>
<li>Fix: Preserve zoom level for leaving/entering map</li>
<li>Fix: Remove temporary downloaded map file after successful copy to c:geo</li>
<li>Fix: Individual route: Update distance on item removal</li>
<li>Fix: Crash on Google Maps map being put into the background</li>
<li>Fix: Global filter in \"live map\" mode</li>
<li>New: Added attribution to contributors on OpenStreetMap maps</li>
<li>New: Added option to show big smileys for found caches</li>
<li>New: Enlarge display of distance to current navigation target by tapping on it</li>
</ul>

<h4>Cache details:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Change: Combine note and user note for export waypoint to GPX, on import split them up</li>
<li>Change: Disable cache detail share menu for user-defined caches</li>
<li>Fix: Hint is not displayed on compass view, when launched directly from map</li>
<li>Fix: Update list of waypoints on extract waypoints</li>
<li>New: provide direct log link ability for gc.com/oc.*/gc.su</li>
<li>New: Support [TYPE] in signature</li>
<li>New: Image upload on logging: always remove EXIF data</li>
<li>New: Image upload on logging: allow resorting images</li>
<li>New: Waypoint calculator: add option to lower-case all variables</li>
<li>New: Show counter for logtext length</li>
<li>Change: Own waypoint with empty coords will be extracted from personal cache note</li>
<li>Change: Harmonize \"share\" menus to system-wide \"share\"</li>
</ul>

<h4>Cache lists:</h4>
<ul>
<li>New: Improved performance for filtering large cache lists</li>
<li>New: Added link to the gc message center in several places</li>
<li>Change: User-defined caches are stored in a separate list \"user-defined caches\" instead of in default list</li>
<li>Fix: avoid crash when trying to log a PM cache as basic member</li>
</ul>

<h4>Other:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Change: Backup / restore caches and settings in one step</li>
<li>New: Preserve multiple backups of caches and settings</li>
<li>Fix: Adapt trackable search to website change on geocaching.com</li>
<li>Fix: Export waypoints even if they have no coordinates</li>
<li>Fix: GPX export of position history: timestamps are now GMT-based</li>
<li>New: GPX export of position history: added elevation info</li>
<li>New: Set/read GSAK "user defined waypoint" flag on GPX export/import (if applicable)</li>
<li>New: Format GPX export file more human-readable</li>
<li>New: Added splash screen</li>
<li>Change: Throw a runtime error if db can neither be opened nor created</li>
<li>New: Automatically convert geocode search input to upper case</li>
<li>New: Select target on geo intents (new user defined cache, waypoint for \"go to\" history, waypoint for existing user defined cache)</li>
<li>Change: Updated widget icons</li>
<li>Updated list of contributors</li>
</ul>
</div>]]></Data>
  </string>
</resources>
